<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?><!DOCTYPE tv SYSTEM "xmltv.dtd">
<tv generator-info-name="XUI.one">
	<channel id="Cinemax5StarMAX.us">
		<display-name>5StarMax US</display-name>
		<icon src="http://cfsystems.io:80/images/bab02c90620932fde2bad7f75110a696.png" />
	</channel>
	<programme start="20230217111101 +0000" stop="20230217124001 +0000" start_timestamp="1676632261" stop_timestamp="1676637601" channel="Cinemax5StarMAX.us" >
		<title>Mannequin</title>
		<desc>Movie (1987)
Jonathan Switcher (Andrew McCarthy), an unemployed artist, finds a job as an assistant window dresser for a department store. When Jonathan happens upon a beautiful mannequin he previously designed, she springs to life and introduces herself as Emmy (Kim Cattrall), an Egyptian under an ancient spell. Despite interference from the store&apos;s devious manager (James Spader), Jonathan and his mannequin fall in love while creating eye-catching window displays to keep the struggling store in business.</desc>
	</programme>
	<programme start="20230217124001 +0000" stop="20230217141301 +0000" start_timestamp="1676637601" stop_timestamp="1676643181" channel="Cinemax5StarMAX.us" >
		<title>Last Night</title>
		<desc>Movie (2010)
Joanna (Keira Knightley) and Michael Reed (Sam Worthington) are a happily married couple. However, the fate of their marriage rests on how each responds to temptation during a night apart. Michael goes away on a business trip with an attractive colleague named Laura (Eva Mendes), whose outer beauty masks a deep loneliness. Slightly jealous, Joanna encounters a former flame (Guillaume Canet) and agrees to meet him for drinks, but the innocent date may become something more.</desc>
	</programme>
	<programme start="20230217141301 +0000" stop="20230217155101 +0000" start_timestamp="1676643181" stop_timestamp="1676649061" channel="Cinemax5StarMAX.us" >
		<title>After the Sunset</title>
		<desc>Movie (2004)
Having already stolen two from the set of three priceless Napoleon Diamonds, expert jewel thief Max Burdett (Pierce Brosnan) decides to retire on a tropical island with his girlfriend and partner-in-crime, Lola (Salma Hayek). Fate intervenes, however, when Max discovers the third and final diamond is sitting on a docked cruise ship on his very island. It should be a simple job, but FBI agent Stan Lloyd (Woody Harrelson) shows up to make sure Max doesn&apos;t get any ideas.</desc>
	</programme>
	<programme start="20230217155101 +0000" stop="20230217174501 +0000" start_timestamp="1676649061" stop_timestamp="1676655901" channel="Cinemax5StarMAX.us" >
		<title>Nostalgia</title>
		<desc>Movie (2018)
The lives of several people become connected through loss.</desc>
	</programme>
	<programme start="20230217174501 +0000" stop="20230217194201 +0000" start_timestamp="1676655901" stop_timestamp="1676662921" channel="Cinemax5StarMAX.us" >
		<title>The Mule</title>
		<desc>Movie (2018)
Broke, alone and facing foreclosure on his business, 90-year-old horticulturist Earl Stone takes a job as a drug courier for a Mexican cartel. His immediate success leads to easy money and a larger shipment that soon draws the attention of hard-charging DEA agent Colin Bates. When Earl&apos;s past mistakes start to weigh heavily on his conscience, he must decide whether to right those wrongs before law enforcement and cartel thugs catch up to him.</desc>
	</programme>
	<programme start="20230217194201 +0000" stop="20230217211901 +0000" start_timestamp="1676662921" stop_timestamp="1676668741" channel="Cinemax5StarMAX.us" >
		<title>Johnson Family Vacation</title>
		<desc>Movie (2004)
Separated from his beautiful wife (Vanessa L. Williams), Nate Johnson (Cedric the Entertainer) wants to make amends with her and spend time with his kids, finding the perfect chance for bonding in a cross-country trip to a family reunion. Convincing them all to join in on the journey, Nate takes the Johnson clan on a trek from California to Missouri, but they encounter various strange situations and eccentrics along the way, including a quirky hitchhiker (Shannon Elizabeth).</desc>
	</programme>
	<programme start="20230217211901 +0000" stop="20230217225101 +0000" start_timestamp="1676668741" stop_timestamp="1676674261" channel="Cinemax5StarMAX.us" >
		<title>Extract</title>
		<desc>Movie (2009)
The owner of a factory that produces flavor extracts, Joel Reynold (Jason Bateman) seems to have it all, but really doesn&apos;t. What&apos;s missing is sexual attention from his wife, Suzie (Kristen Wiig). Joel hatches a convoluted plan to get Suzie to cheat on him, thereby clearing the way for Joel to have an affair with Cindy (Mila Kunis), an employee. But what Joel doesn&apos;t know is that Cindy is a sociopathic con artist, and a freak workplace accident clears the way for her to ruin Joel forever.</desc>
	</programme>
	<programme start="20230217225101 +0000" stop="20230218002801 +0000" start_timestamp="1676674261" stop_timestamp="1676680081" channel="Cinemax5StarMAX.us" >
		<title>Pretty in Pink</title>
		<desc>Movie (1986)
Andie (Molly Ringwald) is an outcast at her Chicago high school, hanging out either with her older boss (Annie Potts), who owns the record store where she works, or her quirky classmate Duckie (Jon Cryer), who has a crush on her. When one of the rich and popular kids at school, Blane (Andrew McCarthy), asks Andie out, it seems too good to be true. As Andie starts falling for Blane, she begins to realizes that dating someone from a different social sphere is not easy.</desc>
	</programme>
	<programme start="20230218002801 +0000" stop="20230218020001 +0000" start_timestamp="1676680081" stop_timestamp="1676685601" channel="Cinemax5StarMAX.us" >
		<title>A Thousand Words</title>
		<desc>Movie (2012)
Jack McCall (Eddie Murphy) is a selfish literary agent whose fast-talking ways allow him to close any deal. His next target is New Age guru Dr. Sinja (Cliff Curtis), but the savvy doctor sees right through Jack. A magical tree appears in Jack&apos;s yard, and, according to Dr. Sinja, the tree and Jack are connected; every time Jack says a word, a leaf falls from the tree. When the last leaf drops, Jack will die. With just a thousand leaves left, Jack must learn to curb his speech or he&apos;s a goner.</desc>
	</programme>
	<programme start="20230218020001 +0000" stop="20230218035001 +0000" start_timestamp="1676685601" stop_timestamp="1676692201" channel="Cinemax5StarMAX.us" >
		<title>We&apos;re the Millers</title>
		<desc>Movie (2013)
Small-time pot dealer David (Jason Sudeikis) learns the hard way that no good deed goes unpunished; trying to help some teens, he is jumped by thugs and loses his cash and stash. Now, David&apos;s in big debt to his supplier and -- to wipe the slate clean -- he must go to Mexico to pick up the guy&apos;s latest shipment. To accomplish his mission, Dave devises a foolproof plan: He packs a fake family into a huge RV and heads south of the border for a wild weekend that is sure to end with a bang.</desc>
	</programme>
	<programme start="20230218035001 +0000" stop="20230218053701 +0000" start_timestamp="1676692201" stop_timestamp="1676698621" channel="Cinemax5StarMAX.us" >
		<title>The Break-Up</title>
		<desc>Movie (2006)
When Brooke (Jennifer Aniston), an art dealer, and Gary (Vince Vaughn), a tour-bus driver, finally call it quits in their relationship, neither is willing to move out of their shared condo. With their friends suggesting a series of underhanded tactics that fail to get either Brooke or Gary to cave in, the only solution is to become hostile roommates.</desc>
	</programme>
	<programme start="20230218053701 +0000" stop="20230218071901 +0000" start_timestamp="1676698621" stop_timestamp="1676704741" channel="Cinemax5StarMAX.us" >
		<title>Because I Said So</title>
		<desc>Movie (2007)
Daphne Wilder (Diane Keaton) is the proud mother of three women: Milly (Mandy Moore), Maggie (Lauren Graham) and Mae (Piper Perabo), and her love for her offspring knows no bounds. Because her youngest, always chooses the wrong man, she decides to take action to prevent Milly from repeating the mistakes of the past. Dating disaster ensues when Daphne tries to achieve her goal by placing an online personal ad for Milly.</desc>
	</programme>
	<programme start="20230218071901 +0000" stop="20230218090801 +0000" start_timestamp="1676704741" stop_timestamp="1676711281" channel="Cinemax5StarMAX.us" >
		<title>Perfect Stranger</title>
		<desc>Movie (2007)
Rowena Price (Halle Berry), a reporter, uses her investigative skills to solve the murder of a friend. Her search leads her to Harrison Hill (Bruce Willis), a high-powered advertising executive. She assumes new identities in the real world and online, utilizing cyberspace in a bid to bring her quarry to justice.</desc>
	</programme>
	<programme start="20230218090801 +0000" stop="20230218111901 +0000" start_timestamp="1676711281" stop_timestamp="1676719141" channel="Cinemax5StarMAX.us" >
		<title>Octopussy</title>
		<desc>Movie (1983)
James Bond (Roger Moore) may have met his match in Octopussy (Maud Adams), an entrancing beauty involved in a devastating military plot to destroy détente. From the palaces of India to a speeding circus train in Germany and a mid-air battle on the wing of a high-flying jet, only Agent 007 can stop the nightmarish scheme!</desc>
	</programme>
	<programme start="20230218111901 +0000" stop="20230218132101 +0000" start_timestamp="1676719141" stop_timestamp="1676726461" channel="Cinemax5StarMAX.us" >
		<title>Hotel Rwanda</title>
		<desc>Movie (2004)
Paul Rusesabagina (Don Cheadle), a Hutu, manages the Hôtel des Mille Collines and lives a happy life with his Tutsi wife (Sophie Okonedo) and their three children. But when Hutu military forces initiate a campaign of ethnic cleansing against the Tutsi minority, Paul is compelled to allow refugees to take shelter in his hotel. As the U.N. pulls out, Paul must struggle alone to protect the Tutsi refugees in the face of the escalating violence later known as the Rwandan genocide.</desc>
	</programme>
	<programme start="20230218132101 +0000" stop="20230218144401 +0000" start_timestamp="1676726461" stop_timestamp="1676731441" channel="Cinemax5StarMAX.us" >
		<title>An American Haunting</title>
		<desc>Movie (2005)
Landowners in 1817 Tennessee, John (Donald Sutherland) and Lucy Bell (Sissy Spacek) experience strange and terrifying events after fellow parishioners find John guilty of loan-sharking and his victim curses the Bell family. The incidents culminate in the daughter&apos;s (Rachel Hurd-Wood) apparent possession by demons.</desc>
	</programme>
	<programme start="20230218144401 +0000" stop="20230218164401 +0000" start_timestamp="1676731441" stop_timestamp="1676738641" channel="Cinemax5StarMAX.us" >
		<title>Mona Lisa Smile</title>
		<desc>Movie (2003)
Katherine Watson (Julia Roberts) is a recent UCLA graduate hired to teach art history at the prestigious all-female Wellesley College, in 1953. Determined to confront the outdated mores of society and the institution that embraces them, Katherine inspires her traditional students including Betty (Kirsten Dunst) and Joan (Julia Stiles) to challenge the lives they are expected to lead.</desc>
	</programme>
	<programme start="20230218164401 +0000" stop="20230218183801 +0000" start_timestamp="1676738641" stop_timestamp="1676745481" channel="Cinemax5StarMAX.us" >
		<title>Gone Baby Gone</title>
		<desc>Movie (2007)
Along with his girlfriend (Michelle Monaghan), a private detective (Casey Affleck) takes on the difficult task of searching for a kidnapped girl in Boston. During his investigation, he must deal with the girl&apos;s aunt, a disapproving lawman (Morgan Freeman) and a drug dealer.</desc>
	</programme>
	<programme start="20230218183801 +0000" stop="20230218202201 +0000" start_timestamp="1676745481" stop_timestamp="1676751721" channel="Cinemax5StarMAX.us" >
		<title>Along Came a Spider</title>
		<desc>Movie (2001)
A psychological suspense thriller adapted from James Patterson&apos;s first highly acclaimed novel in the Alex Cross series, Morgan Freeman reprises his role as the Washington, D.C. police detective and psychologist who is through playing mind games with criminals -- that is until a methodical predator, Gary Soneji (Michael Wincott) commits a daring kidnapping and lures Cross into the case.</desc>
	</programme>
	<programme start="20230218202201 +0000" stop="20230218203801 +0000" start_timestamp="1676751721" stop_timestamp="1676752681" channel="Cinemax5StarMAX.us" >
		<title>Unmothered</title>
		<desc>Movie (2020)
A rebellious American woman discovers a serious secret about her funny family when she returns to India to immerse her mother&apos;s ashes.</desc>
	</programme>
	<programme start="20230218203801 +0000" stop="20230218224801 +0000" start_timestamp="1676752681" stop_timestamp="1676760481" channel="Cinemax5StarMAX.us" >
		<title>W.</title>
		<desc>Movie (2008)
Flashbacks to key events in his life reveal the rise of George W. Bush from ne&apos;er-do-well party boy and son of privilege to president of the United States. After trading in booze for religion, George mends his aimless ways and sets his sights first on the Texas governorship, then on the presidency. But the country&apos;s involvement in the Iraq war decreases his approval rating.</desc>
	</programme>
	<programme start="20230218224801 +0000" stop="20230219003301 +0000" start_timestamp="1676760481" stop_timestamp="1676766781" channel="Cinemax5StarMAX.us" >
		<title>Delivery Man</title>
		<desc>Movie (2013)
Amiable slacker David Wozniak (Vince Vaughn) drives a delivery truck for his family&apos;s company and is content with a life of mediocrity. However, when he learns that he is the biological father of more than 500 offspring and many of them are suing to learn his identity, he decides to hold himself accountable for his actions. He finds some of his progeny and becomes involved in their lives; however, when David&apos;s girlfriend announces her pregnancy, she keeps her expectations low.</desc>
	</programme>
	<programme start="20230219003301 +0000" stop="20230219020001 +0000" start_timestamp="1676766781" stop_timestamp="1676772001" channel="Cinemax5StarMAX.us" >
		<title>Black Sheep</title>
		<desc>Movie (1996)
Mike (Chris Farley), a slovenly gym teacher, has a terrible habit of showing up at the wrong time and embarrassing his brother, Al (Tim Matheson), who happens to be running for governor. Hoping to save his campaign, Al assigns his aide, Steve (David Spade), to take Mike to a remote cabin and hide out there for the remainder of the campaign. In the woods, the two men discover dangers that make them long for the sleazy political operatives back in the big city.</desc>
	</programme>
	<programme start="20230219020001 +0000" stop="20230219035201 +0000" start_timestamp="1676772001" stop_timestamp="1676778721" channel="Cinemax5StarMAX.us" >
		<title>The Card Counter</title>
		<desc>Movie (2021)
A gambler attempts to give guidance to a young man who is out for revenge against a mutual enemy.</desc>
	</programme>
	<programme start="20230219035201 +0000" stop="20230219053801 +0000" start_timestamp="1676778721" stop_timestamp="1676785081" channel="Cinemax5StarMAX.us" >
		<title>Halloween Kills</title>
		<desc>Movie (2021)
The nightmare isn&apos;t over as unstoppable killer Michael Myers escapes from Laurie Strode&apos;s trap to continue his ritual bloodbath. Injured and taken to the hospital, Laurie reunites with Tommy Doyle, the boy she was babysitting on the night Michael began his reign of terror. As Laurie continues to fight through the pain, Tommy leads an angry mob of vigilantes to rise up against Myers and destroy the evil once and for all.</desc>
	</programme>
	<programme start="20230219053801 +0000" stop="20230219072401 +0000" start_timestamp="1676785081" stop_timestamp="1676791441" channel="Cinemax5StarMAX.us" >
		<title>Abduction</title>
		<desc>Movie (2011)
For many years, Nathan Harper (Taylor Lautner) has had the uneasy feeling that life with his family isn&apos;t quite what it seems. His fears come true when he finds a picture of himself as a youngster on a missing-persons website, proof that the people he&apos;s called mom and dad his whole life are not his real parents. As he draws close to uncovering his true identity, Nathan becomes the target of assassins, forcing him to flee with his neighbor, Karen (Lily Collins), the only person he can now trust.</desc>
	</programme>
	<programme start="20230219072401 +0000" stop="20230219090801 +0000" start_timestamp="1676791441" stop_timestamp="1676797681" channel="Cinemax5StarMAX.us" >
		<title>Girl Most Likely</title>
		<desc>Movie (2012)
After losing her job and her boyfriend, a woman (Kristen Wiig) moves in with her estranged mother (Annette Bening) and finds an assortment of strange characters inhabiting the home.</desc>
	</programme>
	<programme start="20230219090801 +0000" stop="20230219111201 +0000" start_timestamp="1676797681" stop_timestamp="1676805121" channel="Cinemax5StarMAX.us" >
		<title>Only Lovers Left Alive</title>
		<desc>Movie (2013)
Artistic, sophisticated and centuries old, two vampire lovers (Tilda Swinton, Tom Hiddleston) ponder their ultimate place in modern society.</desc>
	</programme>
	<programme start="20230219111201 +0000" stop="20230219140501 +0000" start_timestamp="1676805121" stop_timestamp="1676815501" channel="Cinemax5StarMAX.us" >
		<title>The Great Escape</title>
		<desc>Movie (1963)
Imprisoned during World War II in a German POW camp, a group of Allied soldiers are intent on breaking out, not only to escape, but also to draw Nazi forces away from battle to search for fugitives. Among the prisoners determined to escape are American Captain Virgil Hilts (Steve McQueen) and British Squadron Leader Roger Bartlett (Richard Attenborough). Outwitting their captors by digging a tunnel out of the prison grounds, the soldiers find the stakes much higher when escape becomes a reality.</desc>
	</programme>
	<programme start="20230219140501 +0000" stop="20230219154601 +0000" start_timestamp="1676815501" stop_timestamp="1676821561" channel="Cinemax5StarMAX.us" >
		<title>What They Had</title>
		<desc>Movie (2018)
After her ailing mother wanders off during a blizzard, Bridget returns to her childhood home in Chicago, accompanied by her rebellious daughter. Forced to referee between her father&apos;s stubborn insistence that his wife remains at home and her equally determined brother&apos;s efforts to place her in a &quot;memory care&quot; facility, Bridget struggles to make sense of a lifetime of family conflict. With her mother&apos;s decline becoming increasingly obvious, long-simmering resentments bubble to the surface.</desc>
	</programme>
	<programme start="20230219154601 +0000" stop="20230219172301 +0000" start_timestamp="1676821561" stop_timestamp="1676827381" channel="Cinemax5StarMAX.us" >
		<title>Next</title>
		<desc>Movie (2007)
Blessed, or cursed, with the ability to see events minutes before they occur, Cris Johnson (Nicolas Cage) earns a living as a magician in Las Vegas and keeps a low profile under an alias. When terrorists threaten to detonate a nuclear weapon in Los Angeles, government agent Callie Ferris (Julianne Moore) goes on the hunt for Cris and hopes to convince him to help her stop the coming apocalypse.</desc>
	</programme>
	<programme start="20230219172301 +0000" stop="20230219192201 +0000" start_timestamp="1676827381" stop_timestamp="1676834521" channel="Cinemax5StarMAX.us" >
		<title>The Bourne Identity</title>
		<desc>Movie (2002)
The story of a man (Matt Damon), salvaged, near death, from the ocean by an Italian fishing boat. When he recuperates, the man suffers from total amnesia, without identity or background... except for a range of extraordinary talents in fighting, linguistic skills and self-defense that speak of a dangerous past. He sets out on a desperate search-assisted by the initially rebellious Marie (Franka Potente) - to discover who he really is, and why he&apos;s being lethally pursued by assassins.</desc>
	</programme>
	<programme start="20230219192201 +0000" stop="20230219210801 +0000" start_timestamp="1676834521" stop_timestamp="1676840881" channel="Cinemax5StarMAX.us" >
		<title>Alfie</title>
		<desc>Movie (2004)
British-born ladies&apos; man Alfie (Jude Law) exploits his job as a New York City limousine driver to meet and sleep with attractive women -- which infuriates his pseudo-girlfriend Julie (Marisa Tomei), a single mom. His libertine lifestyle is interrupted, however, when his girl-crazy ways end up hurting his best friend, Marlon (Omar Epps). Desperate, Alfie attempts a go at monogamy with the ravishing Nikki (Sienna Miller), but even her good looks aren&apos;t enough to keep him out of trouble for long.</desc>
	</programme>
	<programme start="20230219210801 +0000" stop="20230219224501 +0000" start_timestamp="1676840881" stop_timestamp="1676846701" channel="Cinemax5StarMAX.us" >
		<title>Tommy Boy</title>
		<desc>Movie (1995)
After his beloved father (Brian Dennehy) dies, dimwitted Tommy Callahan (Chris Farley) inherits a near-bankrupt automobile parts factory in Sandusky, Ohio. His brand new stepmother, Beverly (Bo Derek), wants to cash out and close, but Tommy&apos;s sentimental attachment to his father&apos;s employees spurs him to make one last-ditch effort to find someone who will buy their products. With his father&apos;s tightly wound assistant, Richard (David Spade), in tow, Tommy hits the road to scare up some new clients.</desc>
	</programme>
	<programme start="20230219224501 +0000" stop="20230220002001 +0000" start_timestamp="1676846701" stop_timestamp="1676852401" channel="Cinemax5StarMAX.us" >
		<title>Napoleon Dynamite</title>
		<desc>Movie (2004)
In small-town Preston, Idaho, awkward teen Napoleon Dynamite (Jon Heder) has trouble fitting in. After his grandmother is injured in an accident, his life is made even worse when his strangely nostalgic uncle, Rico (Jon Gries), shows up to keep an eye on him. With no safe haven at home or at school, Napoleon befriends the new kid, Pedro (Efren Ramirez), a morose Hispanic boy who speaks little English. Together the two launch a campaign to run for class president.</desc>
	</programme>
	<programme start="20230220002001 +0000" stop="20230220020001 +0000" start_timestamp="1676852401" stop_timestamp="1676858401" channel="Cinemax5StarMAX.us" >
		<title>The Grand Budapest Hotel</title>
		<desc>Movie (2014)
In the 1930s, the Grand Budapest Hotel is a popular European ski resort, presided over by concierge Gustave H. (Ralph Fiennes). Zero, a junior lobby boy, becomes Gustave&apos;s friend and protege. Gustave prides himself on providing first-class service to the hotel&apos;s guests, including satisfying the sexual needs of the many elderly women who stay there. When one of Gustave&apos;s lovers dies mysteriously, Gustave finds himself the recipient of a priceless painting and the chief suspect in her murder.</desc>
	</programme>
	<programme start="20230220020001 +0000" stop="20230220035201 +0000" start_timestamp="1676858401" stop_timestamp="1676865121" channel="Cinemax5StarMAX.us" >
		<title>Trouble With the Curve</title>
		<desc>Movie (2012)
For decades Gus Lobel (Clint Eastwood) has been one of baseball&apos;s best scouts -- but now his age is catching up with him. Still, he refuses to be benched even though his bosses are questioning his judgment. Tasked with checking out the country&apos;s hottest batting prospect, Gus is forced to accept help from his daughter, Mickey (Amy Adams). Though they haven&apos;t spent time together in years, father and daughter make new discoveries about their shared past, which could change their future.</desc>
	</programme>
	<programme start="20230220035201 +0000" stop="20230220055801 +0000" start_timestamp="1676865121" stop_timestamp="1676872681" channel="Cinemax5StarMAX.us" >
		<title>The Fault in Our Stars</title>
		<desc>Movie (2014)
Hazel Grace Lancaster (Shailene Woodley), a 16-year-old cancer patient, meets and falls in love with Gus Waters (Ansel Elgort), a similarly afflicted teen from her cancer support group. Hazel feels that Gus really understands her. They both share the same acerbic wit and a love of books, especially Grace&apos;s touchstone, &quot;An Imperial Affliction&quot; by Peter Van Houten. When Gus scores an invitation to meet the reclusive author, he and Hazel embark on the adventure of their brief lives.</desc>
	</programme>
	<programme start="20230220055801 +0000" stop="20230220080001 +0000" start_timestamp="1676872681" stop_timestamp="1676880001" channel="Cinemax5StarMAX.us" >
		<title>Hunter Killer</title>
		<desc>Movie (2018)
American submarine Capt. Joe Glass is on the hunt for a U.S. sub in distress in the Arctic Ocean. He soon learns that a secret Russian coup is in the offing, a conspiracy that threatens to dismantle the world order. With crew and country on the line, Glass must assemble an elite group of Navy SEALs to sneak through enemy waters, rescue the kidnapped Russian president and prevent World War III.</desc>
	</programme>
	<programme start="20230220080001 +0000" stop="20230220094401 +0000" start_timestamp="1676880001" stop_timestamp="1676886241" channel="Cinemax5StarMAX.us" >
		<title>Belle</title>
		<desc>Movie (2013)
The illegitimate, mixed-race daughter (Gugu Mbatha-Raw) of a British admiral plays an important role in the campaign to abolish slavery in England.</desc>
	</programme>
	<programme start="20230220094401 +0000" stop="20230220111801 +0000" start_timestamp="1676886241" stop_timestamp="1676891881" channel="Cinemax5StarMAX.us" >
		<title>The Fly</title>
		<desc>Movie (1958)
When scientist Andre Delambre (Al Hedison) tests his matter transporter on himself, an errant housefly makes its way into the transportation chamber, and things go horribly wrong. As a result, Delambre&apos;s head and arm are now that of the insect. Slowly losing himself to the fly, Delambre turns to his wife, Helene (Patricia Owens), for help. But when tragedy strikes, Delambre&apos;s brother (Vincent Price) and Inspector Charas (Herbert Marshall) are forced to pick up the investigation.</desc>
	</programme>
	<programme start="20230220111801 +0000" stop="20230220132801 +0000" start_timestamp="1676891881" stop_timestamp="1676899681" channel="Cinemax5StarMAX.us" >
		<title>Journey to the Center of the Earth</title>
		<desc>Movie (1959)
A geologist (James Mason) and his assistant (Pat Boone) set off on an expedition to the center of the earth. Following directions found in an inscription hidden in volcanic rock, the explorers travel to a volcano in Iceland to begin their journey. Along the way, a widow of a famous scientist (Arlene Dahl) and an Icelander (Peter Ronson) join their party. However, the treacherous terrain and prehistoric monsters are not their only concern when a rival scientist (Thayer David) is on their trail.</desc>
	</programme>
	<programme start="20230220132801 +0000" stop="20230220153701 +0000" start_timestamp="1676899681" stop_timestamp="1676907421" channel="Cinemax5StarMAX.us" >
		<title>Disclosure</title>
		<desc>Movie (1994)
In this Michael Crichton adaptation, Tom Sanders (Michael Douglas) is a senior executive at a cutting-edge technology corporation on the verge of releasing an innovative new product. Sanders&apos; boss, Bob Galvin (Donald Sutherland), is putting the final touches on a potentially lucrative merger and everything is in order for Tom until a vamp from his past, Meredith Johnson (Demi Moore), swoops in, stealing his impending promotion and then -- doubling down -- suing him for sexual harassment.</desc>
	</programme>
	<programme start="20230220153701 +0000" stop="20230220171401 +0000" start_timestamp="1676907421" stop_timestamp="1676913241" channel="Cinemax5StarMAX.us" >
		<title>Pretty in Pink</title>
		<desc>Movie (1986)
Andie (Molly Ringwald) is an outcast at her Chicago high school, hanging out either with her older boss (Annie Potts), who owns the record store where she works, or her quirky classmate Duckie (Jon Cryer), who has a crush on her. When one of the rich and popular kids at school, Blane (Andrew McCarthy), asks Andie out, it seems too good to be true. As Andie starts falling for Blane, she begins to realizes that dating someone from a different social sphere is not easy.</desc>
	</programme>
	<programme start="20230220171401 +0000" stop="20230220190301 +0000" start_timestamp="1676913241" stop_timestamp="1676919781" channel="Cinemax5StarMAX.us" >
		<title>Fools Rush In</title>
		<desc>Movie (1997)
Three months after a one-night stand with Isabel Fuentes (Salma Hayek) in Las Vegas, New York City real estate developer Alex Whitman (Matthew Perry) learns she is pregnant. Despite being a terminal bachelor, Alex is drawn to Isabel, and the pair marries. Isabel&apos;s father, Miguel (Tomas Milian), suspects Alex has bad intentions, and the couple finds themselves pressured by both their families. When Alex is offered a promotion, he is torn between his new life in Las Vegas and success in New York.</desc>
	</programme>
	<programme start="20230220190301 +0000" stop="20230220191901 +0000" start_timestamp="1676919781" stop_timestamp="1676920741" channel="Cinemax5StarMAX.us" >
		<title>Unmothered</title>
		<desc>Movie (2020)
A rebellious American woman discovers a serious secret about her funny family when she returns to India to immerse her mother&apos;s ashes.</desc>
	</programme>
	<programme start="20230220191901 +0000" stop="20230220205501 +0000" start_timestamp="1676920741" stop_timestamp="1676926501" channel="Cinemax5StarMAX.us" >
		<title>Johnson Family Vacation</title>
		<desc>Movie (2004)
Separated from his beautiful wife (Vanessa L. Williams), Nate Johnson (Cedric the Entertainer) wants to make amends with her and spend time with his kids, finding the perfect chance for bonding in a cross-country trip to a family reunion. Convincing them all to join in on the journey, Nate takes the Johnson clan on a trek from California to Missouri, but they encounter various strange situations and eccentrics along the way, including a quirky hitchhiker (Shannon Elizabeth).</desc>
	</programme>
	<programme start="20230220205501 +0000" stop="20230220224501 +0000" start_timestamp="1676926501" stop_timestamp="1676933101" channel="Cinemax5StarMAX.us" >
		<title>We&apos;re the Millers</title>
		<desc>Movie (2013)
Small-time pot dealer David (Jason Sudeikis) learns the hard way that no good deed goes unpunished; trying to help some teens, he is jumped by thugs and loses his cash and stash. Now, David&apos;s in big debt to his supplier and -- to wipe the slate clean -- he must go to Mexico to pick up the guy&apos;s latest shipment. To accomplish his mission, Dave devises a foolproof plan: He packs a fake family into a huge RV and heads south of the border for a wild weekend that is sure to end with a bang.</desc>
	</programme>
	<programme start="20230220224501 +0000" stop="20230221001301 +0000" start_timestamp="1676933101" stop_timestamp="1676938381" channel="Cinemax5StarMAX.us" >
		<title>Throw Momma From the Train</title>
		<desc>Movie (1987)
Larry (Billy Crystal), an author with a cruel ex-wife, Margaret (Kate Mulgrew), teaches a writing workshop where Owen (Danny DeVito), one of his students, is fed up with his domineering mother (Anne Ramsey). When Owen watches a Hitchcock classic that seems to mirror his own life, he decides to put the movie&apos;s plot into action and offers to kill Margaret, if Larry promises to murder his mom. Before Larry gets a chance to react to the plan, it seems that Owen has already sealed Margaret&apos;s fate.</desc>
	</programme>
	<programme start="20230221001301 +0000" stop="20230221020001 +0000" start_timestamp="1676938381" stop_timestamp="1676944801" channel="Cinemax5StarMAX.us" >
		<title>The Break-Up</title>
		<desc>Movie (2006)
When Brooke (Jennifer Aniston), an art dealer, and Gary (Vince Vaughn), a tour-bus driver, finally call it quits in their relationship, neither is willing to move out of their shared condo. With their friends suggesting a series of underhanded tactics that fail to get either Brooke or Gary to cave in, the only solution is to become hostile roommates.</desc>
	</programme>
	<programme start="20230221020001 +0000" stop="20230221040301 +0000" start_timestamp="1676944801" stop_timestamp="1676952181" channel="Cinemax5StarMAX.us" >
		<title>3:10 to Yuma</title>
		<desc>Movie (2007)
Outlaw Ben Wade (Russell Crowe) terrorizes 1800s Arizona, especially the Southern Railroad, until he is finally captured. Wade must be brought to trial, so Dan Evans (Christian Bale), the owner of a drought-stricken ranch, volunteers to escort him to the train. Along the trail, a grudging respect forms between the men, but danger looms at every turn, and the criminal&apos;s men are in pursuit.</desc>
	</programme>
	<programme start="20230221040301 +0000" stop="20230221055201 +0000" start_timestamp="1676952181" stop_timestamp="1676958721" channel="Cinemax5StarMAX.us" >
		<title>The Bourne Supremacy</title>
		<desc>Movie (2004)
Jason Bourne (Matt Damon) is living in India when he is framed by Russian agent Kirill (Karl Urban) for the theft of millions from the CIA. Kirill begins to pursue Bourne, intending to assassinate him -- but while Bourne and his girlfriend, Marie (Franka Potente), are on the run, a shot meant for him kills her instead. Vowing revenge, Bourne sets out to prove his innocence and bring the culprits to justice, but he has to evade CIA head Pamela Landry (Joan Allen), who is convinced he is guilty.</desc>
	</programme>
	<programme start="20230221055201 +0000" stop="20230221071601 +0000" start_timestamp="1676958721" stop_timestamp="1676963761" channel="Cinemax5StarMAX.us" >
		<title>Dude, Where&apos;s My Car?</title>
		<desc>Movie (2000)
Last night, two party-hearty Dudes had an unbelievably sweet time. Too bad, they can&apos;t remember a thing, including where they parked their car. So, the Dudes embark on a mission: retrace their steps to find out what they did last night hoping it will lead them to the missing car. Little do the Dudes know, they&apos;re in for the ride of their lives.</desc>
	</programme>
	<programme start="20230221071601 +0000" stop="20230221083901 +0000" start_timestamp="1676963761" stop_timestamp="1676968741" channel="Cinemax5StarMAX.us" >
		<title>Jeff, Who Lives at Home</title>
		<desc>Movie (2011)
When Jeff (Jason Segel) leaves his mother&apos;s basement to buy wood glue at the store, he looks for signs from the universe to determine his path. However, a series of unexpected and amusing events leads him to cross paths with his family, especially his brother (Ed Helms), in the strangest of circumstances and locations. If Jeff is very lucky and universally blessed, he will find the meaning of his life... and remember to buy the wood glue as well.</desc>
	</programme>
	<programme start="20230221083901 +0000" stop="20230221101201 +0000" start_timestamp="1676968741" stop_timestamp="1676974321" channel="Cinemax5StarMAX.us" >
		<title>From Paris With Love</title>
		<desc>Movie (2010)
James Reese (Jonathan Rhys Meyers) has a good job as an ambassador&apos;s aid in France, but his real passion is a side gig, working in a minor role in the CIA. He would love to be a full-fledged agent and can&apos;t believe his luck when he lands an assignment with Charlie Wax (John Travolta). Trigger-happy Charlie soon has James crying for his desk job, but when he learns that the same guys they&apos;re trying to catch are after him, James realizes that Charlie may be his only hope of survival.</desc>
	</programme>
	<programme start="20230221101201 +0000" stop="20230221114701 +0000" start_timestamp="1676974321" stop_timestamp="1676980021" channel="Cinemax5StarMAX.us" >
		<title>Some Kind of Wonderful</title>
		<desc>Movie (1987)
Keith Nelson (Eric Stoltz), an artsy high school outcast, tries to land a date with popular girl Amanda Jones (Lea Thompson) with some help from his tomboy best friend, Watts (Mary Stuart Masterson). However, his advances draw the ire of Amanda&apos;s snobby ex-boyfriend, Hardy Jenns (Craig Sheffer), who makes plans to get even. Matters are further complicated when Watts realizes she likes Keith as more than just a friend and tries to convince him to stop pursuing Amanda.</desc>
	</programme>
	<programme start="20230221114701 +0000" stop="20230221133801 +0000" start_timestamp="1676980021" stop_timestamp="1676986681" channel="Cinemax5StarMAX.us" >
		<title>Cats</title>
		<desc>Movie (2019)
A tribe of cats must decide yearly which one will ascend to the Heaviside Layer and come back to a new life.</desc>
	</programme>
	<programme start="20230221133801 +0000" stop="20230221153801 +0000" start_timestamp="1676986681" stop_timestamp="1676993881" channel="Cinemax5StarMAX.us" >
		<title>Flash of Genius</title>
		<desc>Movie (2008)
When college professor and part-time inventor Robert Kearns (Greg Kinnear) develops an intermittent windshield wiper, he believes he, his wife (Lauren Graham) and their children will be set for life. Though the invention is a big hit with automakers in 1960s Detroit, Kearns finds himself forced out of the picture. Determined to collect the recognition and financial reward due him, he wages an arduous legal battle with the auto industry.</desc>
	</programme>
	<programme start="20230221153801 +0000" stop="20230221173901 +0000" start_timestamp="1676993881" stop_timestamp="1677001141" channel="Cinemax5StarMAX.us" >
		<title>Valkyrie</title>
		<desc>Movie (2008)
Col. Claus von Stauffenberg (Tom Cruise) serves Germany with loyalty and pride but fears that Hitler will destroy his country if allowed to run unchecked. With time running out for Germany and the rest of Europe, von Stauffenberg joins a group of like-minded, high-ranking men who want to overthrow the Nazi regime from within. With everything he holds dear in the balance, von Stauffenberg becomes the trigger man in a plot to assassinate the evil dictator.</desc>
	</programme>
	<programme start="20230221173901 +0000" stop="20230221204101 +0000" start_timestamp="1677001141" stop_timestamp="1677012061" channel="Cinemax5StarMAX.us" >
		<title>Dances With Wolves</title>
		<desc>Movie (1990)
A Civil War soldier develops a relationship with a band of Lakota Indians. Attracted by the simplicity of their lifestyle, he chooses to leave his former life behind to be with them. Having observed him, they give the name Dances With Wolves. Soon he is a welcomed member of the tribe and falls in love with a white woman who has been raised in the tribe. Tragedy results when Union soldiers arrive with designs on the land.</desc>
	</programme>
	<programme start="20230221204101 +0000" stop="20230221222401 +0000" start_timestamp="1677012061" stop_timestamp="1677018241" channel="Cinemax5StarMAX.us" >
		<title>Mickey Blue Eyes</title>
		<desc>Movie (1999)
English art dealer Michael Felgate (Hugh Grant) is dumbfounded to learn that his girlfriend, Gina Vitale (Jeanne Tripplehorn), cannot accept his marriage proposal because her entire family is involved with the Mafia. Undeterred and in love, Michael meets Gina&apos;s father, mob boss Frank (James Caan), who immediately takes a shine to the young suitor. But before he can give his blessing, Frank has plans for Michael that may or may not end in wedding bells.</desc>
	</programme>
	<programme start="20230221222401 +0000" stop="20230222000601 +0000" start_timestamp="1677018241" stop_timestamp="1677024361" channel="Cinemax5StarMAX.us" >
		<title>Because I Said So</title>
		<desc>Movie (2007)
Daphne Wilder (Diane Keaton) is the proud mother of three women: Milly (Mandy Moore), Maggie (Lauren Graham) and Mae (Piper Perabo), and her love for her offspring knows no bounds. Because her youngest, always chooses the wrong man, she decides to take action to prevent Milly from repeating the mistakes of the past. Dating disaster ensues when Daphne tries to achieve her goal by placing an online personal ad for Milly.</desc>
	</programme>
	<programme start="20230222000601 +0000" stop="20230222020001 +0000" start_timestamp="1677024361" stop_timestamp="1677031201" channel="Cinemax5StarMAX.us" >
		<title>Nostalgia</title>
		<desc>Movie (2018)
The lives of several people become connected through loss.</desc>
	</programme>
	<programme start="20230222020001 +0000" stop="20230222034501 +0000" start_timestamp="1677031201" stop_timestamp="1677037501" channel="Cinemax5StarMAX.us" >
		<title>Limitless</title>
		<desc>Movie (2011)
Facing unemployment and his girlfriend&apos;s rejection, writer Eddie Morra (Bradley Cooper) is sure that he has no future. That all changes when an old friend gives him a drug that produces enhanced mental acuity. Stoked on the untested chemical, Eddie rises to the top of the financial world and attracts the attention of a tycoon (Robert De Niro) who intends to use him to make a fortune. But terrible side-effects and a dwindling supply threaten to collapse Eddie&apos;s house of cards.</desc>
	</programme>
	<programme start="20230222034501 +0000" stop="20230222053401 +0000" start_timestamp="1677037501" stop_timestamp="1677044041" channel="Cinemax5StarMAX.us" >
		<title>Smokin&apos; Aces</title>
		<desc>Movie (2007)
Sleazy entertainer Buddy &quot;Aces&quot; Israel (Jeremy Piven) incurs the wrath of crime boss Primo Sparazza when he agrees to testify against the Las Vegas mob. Two FBI agents (Ray Liotta, Ryan Reynolds) have the difficult task of protecting him from a motley assortment of bounty hunters, hit men and nefarious vixens who are converging on his Lake Tahoe encampment to rub him out and collect a hefty reward.</desc>
	</programme>
	<programme start="20230222053401 +0000" stop="20230222070101 +0000" start_timestamp="1677044041" stop_timestamp="1677049261" channel="Cinemax5StarMAX.us" >
		<title>Black Sheep</title>
		<desc>Movie (1996)
Mike (Chris Farley), a slovenly gym teacher, has a terrible habit of showing up at the wrong time and embarrassing his brother, Al (Tim Matheson), who happens to be running for governor. Hoping to save his campaign, Al assigns his aide, Steve (David Spade), to take Mike to a remote cabin and hide out there for the remainder of the campaign. In the woods, the two men discover dangers that make them long for the sleazy political operatives back in the big city.</desc>
	</programme>
	<programme start="20230222070101 +0000" stop="20230222084701 +0000" start_timestamp="1677049261" stop_timestamp="1677055621" channel="Cinemax5StarMAX.us" >
		<title>Narc</title>
		<desc>Movie (2002)
Tells the dark story of suspended undercover narcotics officer, Nick Tellis (Jason Patric), who is reluctantly drawn back onto the force to find the truth behind the murder of a young police officer killed in the line of duty. He is teamed with Henry Oak (Ray Liotta), the slain officer&apos;s partner, a rogue cop who will stop at nothing to avenge his friend&apos;s death. As Tellis and Oak unravel the case, the dark underbelly of the narcotics world reveals itself in surprising ways.</desc>
	</programme>
	<programme start="20230222084701 +0000" stop="20230222110001 +0000" start_timestamp="1677055621" stop_timestamp="1677063601" channel="Cinemax5StarMAX.us" >
		<title>Brooklyn&apos;s Finest</title>
		<desc>Movie (2009)
A massive drug operation changes the lives of three conflicted New York cops. Burned-out vet Eddie Dugan (Richard Gere) is close to retirement; narcotics cop Sal Procida (Ethan Hawke) faces the difficult task of caring for his large family on his ordinary salary; undercover officer Clarence &quot;Tango&quot; Butler (Don Cheadle) finds his loyalties beginning to shift toward a powerful drug dealer. Over seven chaotic days, the three men are drawn toward a fateful crime and destiny.</desc>
	</programme>
	<programme start="20230222110001 +0000" stop="20230222130001 +0000" start_timestamp="1677063601" stop_timestamp="1677070801" channel="Cinemax5StarMAX.us" >
		<title>The Turning Point</title>
		<desc>Movie (1977)
Forced to give up ballet after becoming pregnant, Deedee (Shirley MacLaine) moved from New York to Oklahoma to raise a family with her husband (Tom Skerritt). When her old friend and fellow ballerina, Emma (Anne Bancroft), comes to town with her dance company and invites Deedee&apos;s daughter, Emilia (Leslie Browne), to join, Deedee is both excited for her daughter and nostalgic for her past life as a dancer. Jealousy and regret rise to the surface as Deedee copes with her buried dreams.</desc>
	</programme>
	<programme start="20230222130001 +0000" stop="20230222144301 +0000" start_timestamp="1677070801" stop_timestamp="1677076981" channel="Cinemax5StarMAX.us" >
		<title>The First Wives Club</title>
		<desc>Movie (1996)
Despondent over the marriage of her ex-husband to a younger woman, a middle-aged divorcée plunges to her death from her penthouse. At the woman&apos;s funeral, her former college friends (Bette Midler, Goldie Hawn, Diane Keaton) reunite for the first time in nearly 30 years. When the three discover the reason for their friend&apos;s suicide, they realize that all of their ex-husbands have taken them for granted -- and deciding it&apos;s time for revenge, they make a pact to get back at their exes.</desc>
	</programme>
	<programme start="20230222144301 +0000" stop="20230222163901 +0000" start_timestamp="1677076981" stop_timestamp="1677083941" channel="Cinemax5StarMAX.us" >
		<title>The Heartbreak Kid</title>
		<desc>Movie (2007)
After a short fling with a beautiful woman named Lila (Malin Akerman) and at the urging of his friends and family, Eddie (Ben Stiller) proposes marriage. But Eddie didn&apos;t realize that Lila is a shrew, and she reveals her true nature during their honeymoon. He then meets Miranda (Michelle Monaghan) and is convinced she is his soul mate. Eddie sets out to woo Miranda and extricate himself from his wife&apos;s claws.</desc>
	</programme>
	<programme start="20230222163901 +0000" stop="20230222182701 +0000" start_timestamp="1677083941" stop_timestamp="1677090421" channel="Cinemax5StarMAX.us" >
		<title>Suite Française</title>
		<desc>Movie (2014)
Her husband away at war, a lonely Frenchwoman (Michelle Williams) begins a tentative romance with the refined German soldier (Matthias Schoenaerts) who has taken up residence in her mother-in-law&apos;s house.</desc>
	</programme>
	<programme start="20230222182701 +0000" stop="20230222203601 +0000" start_timestamp="1677090421" stop_timestamp="1677098161" channel="Cinemax5StarMAX.us" >
		<title>Disclosure</title>
		<desc>Movie (1994)
In this Michael Crichton adaptation, Tom Sanders (Michael Douglas) is a senior executive at a cutting-edge technology corporation on the verge of releasing an innovative new product. Sanders&apos; boss, Bob Galvin (Donald Sutherland), is putting the final touches on a potentially lucrative merger and everything is in order for Tom until a vamp from his past, Meredith Johnson (Demi Moore), swoops in, stealing his impending promotion and then -- doubling down -- suing him for sexual harassment.</desc>
	</programme>
	<programme start="20230222203601 +0000" stop="20230222220701 +0000" start_timestamp="1677098161" stop_timestamp="1677103621" channel="Cinemax5StarMAX.us" >
		<title>Iris</title>
		<desc>Movie (2001)
Two of the most acclaimed actresses of our time, Judi Dench and Kate Winslet, bring to the screen one of the most extraordinary women of her generation, celebrated author, Iris Murdoch. From her days as a brilliant scholar at Oxford, where she thrilled the world around her with her libertine spirit, through her career as a philosopher and novelist, Iris was truly ahead of her time.</desc>
	</programme>
	<programme start="20230222220701 +0000" stop="20230223001301 +0000" start_timestamp="1677103621" stop_timestamp="1677111181" channel="Cinemax5StarMAX.us" >
		<title>The Fault in Our Stars</title>
		<desc>Movie (2014)
Hazel Grace Lancaster (Shailene Woodley), a 16-year-old cancer patient, meets and falls in love with Gus Waters (Ansel Elgort), a similarly afflicted teen from her cancer support group. Hazel feels that Gus really understands her. They both share the same acerbic wit and a love of books, especially Grace&apos;s touchstone, &quot;An Imperial Affliction&quot; by Peter Van Houten. When Gus scores an invitation to meet the reclusive author, he and Hazel embark on the adventure of their brief lives.</desc>
	</programme>
	<programme start="20230223001301 +0000" stop="20230223020001 +0000" start_timestamp="1677111181" stop_timestamp="1677117601" channel="Cinemax5StarMAX.us" >
		<title>The Break-Up</title>
		<desc>Movie (2006)
When Brooke (Jennifer Aniston), an art dealer, and Gary (Vince Vaughn), a tour-bus driver, finally call it quits in their relationship, neither is willing to move out of their shared condo. With their friends suggesting a series of underhanded tactics that fail to get either Brooke or Gary to cave in, the only solution is to become hostile roommates.</desc>
	</programme>
	<programme start="20230223020001 +0000" stop="20230223035001 +0000" start_timestamp="1677117601" stop_timestamp="1677124201" channel="Cinemax5StarMAX.us" >
		<title>Fools Rush In</title>
		<desc>Movie (1997)
Three months after a one-night stand with Isabel Fuentes (Salma Hayek) in Las Vegas, New York City real estate developer Alex Whitman (Matthew Perry) learns she is pregnant. Despite being a terminal bachelor, Alex is drawn to Isabel, and the pair marries. Isabel&apos;s father, Miguel (Tomas Milian), suspects Alex has bad intentions, and the couple finds themselves pressured by both their families. When Alex is offered a promotion, he is torn between his new life in Las Vegas and success in New York.</desc>
	</programme>
	<programme start="20230223035001 +0000" stop="20230223052501 +0000" start_timestamp="1677124201" stop_timestamp="1677129901" channel="Cinemax5StarMAX.us" >
		<title>Napoleon Dynamite</title>
		<desc>Movie (2004)
In small-town Preston, Idaho, awkward teen Napoleon Dynamite (Jon Heder) has trouble fitting in. After his grandmother is injured in an accident, his life is made even worse when his strangely nostalgic uncle, Rico (Jon Gries), shows up to keep an eye on him. With no safe haven at home or at school, Napoleon befriends the new kid, Pedro (Efren Ramirez), a morose Hispanic boy who speaks little English. Together the two launch a campaign to run for class president.</desc>
	</programme>
	<programme start="20230223052501 +0000" stop="20230223072201 +0000" start_timestamp="1677129901" stop_timestamp="1677136921" channel="Cinemax5StarMAX.us" >
		<title>Boomerang</title>
		<desc>Movie (1992)
A cocky ad executive, Marcus (Eddie Murphy) has a reputation as a ladies&apos; man. However, Marcus gets a taste of his own medicine when a merger finds him working under the beautiful Jacqueline (Robin Givens), who has a similarly cavalier attitude about romance. Marcus and Jacqueline become involved, but he is put off by her noncommittal approach to their relationship. Meanwhile, Marcus also begins to develop feelings for the pretty Angela (Halle Berry), who is more thoughtful than Jacqueline.</desc>
	</programme>
	<programme start="20230223072201 +0000" stop="20230223090901 +0000" start_timestamp="1677136921" stop_timestamp="1677143341" channel="Cinemax5StarMAX.us" >
		<title>Mindhunters</title>
		<desc>Movie (2004)
FBI agent Jake Harris (Val Kilmer) escorts a group of cadets to a remote island for simulation training. The cadets, under the leadership of J.D. (Christian Slater), will try to catch an imaginary serial killer within the island&apos;s elaborate facility. The FBI, however, is suspicious of Harris&apos; methods and dispatch Gabe Jensen (LL Cool J) to act as an outside observer. What he finds is a simulation exercise that becomes dangerously real and training that becomes a fight for survival.</desc>
	</programme>
	<programme start="20230223090901 +0000" stop="20230223111701 +0000" start_timestamp="1677143341" stop_timestamp="1677151021" channel="Cinemax5StarMAX.us" >
		<title>Stardust</title>
		<desc>Movie (2007)
To win the heart of his beloved (Sienna Miller), a young man named Tristan (Charlie Cox) ventures into the realm of fairies to retrieve a fallen star. What Tristan finds, however, is not a chunk of space rock, but a woman (Claire Danes) named Yvaine. Yvaine is in great danger, for the king&apos;s sons need her powers to secure the throne, and an evil witch (Michelle Pfeiffer) wants to use her to achieve eternal youth and beauty.</desc>
	</programme>
	<programme start="20230223111701 +0000" stop="20230223125101 +0000" start_timestamp="1677151021" stop_timestamp="1677156661" channel="Cinemax5StarMAX.us" >
		<title>The Fly</title>
		<desc>Movie (1958)
When scientist Andre Delambre (Al Hedison) tests his matter transporter on himself, an errant housefly makes its way into the transportation chamber, and things go horribly wrong. As a result, Delambre&apos;s head and arm are now that of the insect. Slowly losing himself to the fly, Delambre turns to his wife, Helene (Patricia Owens), for help. But when tragedy strikes, Delambre&apos;s brother (Vincent Price) and Inspector Charas (Herbert Marshall) are forced to pick up the investigation.</desc>
	</programme>
	<programme start="20230223125101 +0000" stop="20230223145201 +0000" start_timestamp="1677156661" stop_timestamp="1677163921" channel="Cinemax5StarMAX.us" >
		<title>The Rookie</title>
		<desc>Movie (1990)
Police Det. Nick Pulovski (Clint Eastwood) isn&apos;t so happy when he gets paired with young rookie David Ackerman (Charlie Sheen). Ackerman should have cause for concern too: Most of Pulovski&apos;s partners have ended up in body bags. But they&apos;ll have to get along if they want to take down the car-theft ring whose leaders (Raul Julia, Sonia Braga) are responsible for the death of the veteran&apos;s last partner. Does it matter that Pulovski&apos;s been pulled off the case? Not a bit.</desc>
	</programme>
	<programme start="20230223145201 +0000" stop="20230223164801 +0000" start_timestamp="1677163921" stop_timestamp="1677170881" channel="Cinemax5StarMAX.us" >
		<title>Return to Me</title>
		<desc>Movie (2000)
Heartbroken and struggling emotionally after his wife&apos;s death in a car accident, Bob Rueland (David Duchovny) agrees to go on a blind date set up by his friend Charlie (David Alan Grier). Though the date fizzles, sparks fly between Bob and the waitress, Grace (Minnie Driver), a recovered heart transplant patient with intimacy problems of her own. When Bob discovers Grace&apos;s heart came from his own organ donor wife, an unusual romance blossoms between the two.</desc>
	</programme>
	<programme start="20230223164801 +0000" stop="20230223181401 +0000" start_timestamp="1677170881" stop_timestamp="1677176041" channel="Cinemax5StarMAX.us" >
		<title>Stealing Harvard</title>
		<desc>Movie (2002)
John (Jason Lee) is a hard-working guy who only wants to marry his longtime girlfriend Elaine (Leslie Mann). Elaine and John have vowed to marry once they save $30,000 for their dream house. Things are fine until John&apos;s sister calls to remind him of his promise to pay his niece&apos;s tuition, which costs $29,829 and is due in two weeks! John turns to his friend Duff (Tom Green) to help him make $30,000 quickly. Duff convinces John to make a short-term commitment to petty crime.</desc>
	</programme>
	<programme start="20230223181401 +0000" stop="20230223195901 +0000" start_timestamp="1677176041" stop_timestamp="1677182341" channel="Cinemax5StarMAX.us" >
		<title>Delivery Man</title>
		<desc>Movie (2013)
Amiable slacker David Wozniak (Vince Vaughn) drives a delivery truck for his family&apos;s company and is content with a life of mediocrity. However, when he learns that he is the biological father of more than 500 offspring and many of them are suing to learn his identity, he decides to hold himself accountable for his actions. He finds some of his progeny and becomes involved in their lives; however, when David&apos;s girlfriend announces her pregnancy, she keeps her expectations low.</desc>
	</programme>
	<programme start="20230223195901 +0000" stop="20230223212401 +0000" start_timestamp="1677182341" stop_timestamp="1677187441" channel="Cinemax5StarMAX.us" >
		<title>Another Me</title>
		<desc>Movie (2013)
Fay&apos;s (Sophie Turner) life slowly unravels when she is stalked by a mysterious double who is out to steal her identity and life.</desc>
	</programme>
	<programme start="20230223212401 +0000" stop="20230223224701 +0000" start_timestamp="1677187441" stop_timestamp="1677192421" channel="Cinemax5StarMAX.us" >
		<title>An American Haunting</title>
		<desc>Movie (2005)
Landowners in 1817 Tennessee, John (Donald Sutherland) and Lucy Bell (Sissy Spacek) experience strange and terrifying events after fellow parishioners find John guilty of loan-sharking and his victim curses the Bell family. The incidents culminate in the daughter&apos;s (Rachel Hurd-Wood) apparent possession by demons.</desc>
	</programme>
	<programme start="20230223224701 +0000" stop="20230224002401 +0000" start_timestamp="1677192421" stop_timestamp="1677198241" channel="Cinemax5StarMAX.us" >
		<title>Tommy Boy</title>
		<desc>Movie (1995)
After his beloved father (Brian Dennehy) dies, dimwitted Tommy Callahan (Chris Farley) inherits a near-bankrupt automobile parts factory in Sandusky, Ohio. His brand new stepmother, Beverly (Bo Derek), wants to cash out and close, but Tommy&apos;s sentimental attachment to his father&apos;s employees spurs him to make one last-ditch effort to find someone who will buy their products. With his father&apos;s tightly wound assistant, Richard (David Spade), in tow, Tommy hits the road to scare up some new clients.</desc>
	</programme>
	<programme start="20230224002401 +0000" stop="20230224020001 +0000" start_timestamp="1677198241" stop_timestamp="1677204001" channel="Cinemax5StarMAX.us" >
		<title>The Con Is On</title>
		<desc>Movie (2018)
In an effort to avoid paying off a massive gambling debt to a notorious mobster in England, two badly behaved con artists flee to Los Angeles, where they hatch a convoluted plot to steal jewels.</desc>
	</programme>
	<programme start="20230224020001 +0000" stop="20230224041301 +0000" start_timestamp="1677204001" stop_timestamp="1677211981" channel="Cinemax5StarMAX.us" >
		<title>Miami Vice</title>
		<desc>Movie (2006)
A case involving drug lords and murder in South Florida takes a personal turn for undercover detectives Sonny Crockett (Colin Farrell) and Ricardo Tubbs (Jamie Foxx). Unorthodox Crockett gets involved romantically with the Chinese-Cuban wife of a trafficker of arms and drugs, while Tubbs deals with an assault on those he loves.</desc>
	</programme>
	<programme start="20230224041301 +0000" stop="20230224054401 +0000" start_timestamp="1677211981" stop_timestamp="1677217441" channel="Cinemax5StarMAX.us" >
		<title>Gravity</title>
		<desc>Movie (2013)
Dr. Ryan Stone (Sandra Bullock) is a medical engineer on her first shuttle mission. Her commander is veteran astronaut Matt Kowalsky (George Clooney), helming his last flight before retirement. Then, during a routine space walk by the pair, disaster strikes: The shuttle is destroyed, leaving Ryan and Matt stranded in deep space with no link to Earth and no hope of rescue. As fear turns to panic, they realize that the only way home may be to venture further into space.</desc>
	</programme>
	<programme start="20230224054401 +0000" stop="20230224074101 +0000" start_timestamp="1677217441" stop_timestamp="1677224461" channel="Cinemax5StarMAX.us" >
		<title>The Mule</title>
		<desc>Movie (2018)
Broke, alone and facing foreclosure on his business, 90-year-old horticulturist Earl Stone takes a job as a drug courier for a Mexican cartel. His immediate success leads to easy money and a larger shipment that soon draws the attention of hard-charging DEA agent Colin Bates. When Earl&apos;s past mistakes start to weigh heavily on his conscience, he must decide whether to right those wrongs before law enforcement and cartel thugs catch up to him.</desc>
	</programme>
	<programme start="20230224074101 +0000" stop="20230224095001 +0000" start_timestamp="1677224461" stop_timestamp="1677232201" channel="Cinemax5StarMAX.us" >
		<title>Live Free or Die Hard</title>
		<desc>Movie (2007)
As the nation prepares to celebrate Independence Day, veteran cop John McClane (Bruce Willis) carries out another routine assignment: bringing in a computer hacker (Justin Long) for questioning. Meanwhile, a tech-savvy villain named Thomas Gabriel (Timothy Olyphant) launches an attack on America&apos;s computer infrastructure. As chaos descends around him, McClane must use old-fashioned methods to fight the high-tech threat.</desc>
	</programme>
	<programme start="20230224095001 +0000" stop="20230224113101 +0000" start_timestamp="1677232201" stop_timestamp="1677238261" channel="Cinemax5StarMAX.us" >
		<title>What They Had</title>
		<desc>Movie (2018)
After her ailing mother wanders off during a blizzard, Bridget returns to her childhood home in Chicago, accompanied by her rebellious daughter. Forced to referee between her father&apos;s stubborn insistence that his wife remains at home and her equally determined brother&apos;s efforts to place her in a &quot;memory care&quot; facility, Bridget struggles to make sense of a lifetime of family conflict. With her mother&apos;s decline becoming increasingly obvious, long-simmering resentments bubble to the surface.</desc>
	</programme>
	<programme start="20230224113101 +0000" stop="20230224134501 +0000" start_timestamp="1677238261" stop_timestamp="1677246301" channel="Cinemax5StarMAX.us" >
		<title>Rain Man</title>
		<desc>Movie (1988)
When car dealer Charlie Babbitt (Tom Cruise) learns that his estranged father has died, he returns home to Cincinnati, where he discovers that he has an autistic older brother named Raymond (Dustin Hoffman) and that his father&apos;s $3 million fortune is being left to the mental institution in which Raymond lives. Motivated by his father&apos;s money, Charlie checks Raymond out of the facility in order to return with him to Los Angeles. The brothers&apos; cross-country trip ends up changing both their lives.</desc>
	</programme>
	<programme start="20230224134501 +0000" stop="20230224153401 +0000" start_timestamp="1677246301" stop_timestamp="1677252841" channel="Cinemax5StarMAX.us" >
		<title>The Bourne Supremacy</title>
		<desc>Movie (2004)
Jason Bourne (Matt Damon) is living in India when he is framed by Russian agent Kirill (Karl Urban) for the theft of millions from the CIA. Kirill begins to pursue Bourne, intending to assassinate him -- but while Bourne and his girlfriend, Marie (Franka Potente), are on the run, a shot meant for him kills her instead. Vowing revenge, Bourne sets out to prove his innocence and bring the culprits to justice, but he has to evade CIA head Pamela Landry (Joan Allen), who is convinced he is guilty.</desc>
	</programme>
	<programme start="20230224153401 +0000" stop="20230224171401 +0000" start_timestamp="1677252841" stop_timestamp="1677258841" channel="Cinemax5StarMAX.us" >
		<title>Ride Along</title>
		<desc>Movie (2014)
For two years, security guard Ben (Kevin Hart) has tried to convince James (Ice Cube), a veteran cop, that he is worthy of James&apos; sister, Angela. When Ben is finally accepted into the police academy, James decides to test his mettle by inviting him along on a shift deliberately designed to scare the trainee. However, events take an unexpected turn when their wild night leads to Atlanta&apos;s most-notorious criminal and Ben&apos;s rapid-fire mouth proves as dangerous as the bullets whizzing by them.</desc>
	</programme>
	<programme start="20230224171401 +0000" stop="20230224185901 +0000" start_timestamp="1677258841" stop_timestamp="1677265141" channel="Cinemax5StarMAX.us" >
		<title>A Walk in the Woods</title>
		<desc>Movie (2015)
Travel writer Bill Bryson (Robert Redford) takes a long-lost old friend (Nick Nolte) for a hike along the Appalachian Trail, which stretches more than 2,000 miles from Georgia to Maine.</desc>
	</programme>
	<programme start="20230224185901 +0000" stop="20230224203401 +0000" start_timestamp="1677265141" stop_timestamp="1677270841" channel="Cinemax5StarMAX.us" >
		<title>Napoleon Dynamite</title>
		<desc>Movie (2004)
In small-town Preston, Idaho, awkward teen Napoleon Dynamite (Jon Heder) has trouble fitting in. After his grandmother is injured in an accident, his life is made even worse when his strangely nostalgic uncle, Rico (Jon Gries), shows up to keep an eye on him. With no safe haven at home or at school, Napoleon befriends the new kid, Pedro (Efren Ramirez), a morose Hispanic boy who speaks little English. Together the two launch a campaign to run for class president.</desc>
	</programme>
	<programme start="20230224203401 +0000" stop="20230224221401 +0000" start_timestamp="1677270841" stop_timestamp="1677276841" channel="Cinemax5StarMAX.us" >
		<title>The Grand Budapest Hotel</title>
		<desc>Movie (2014)
In the 1930s, the Grand Budapest Hotel is a popular European ski resort, presided over by concierge Gustave H. (Ralph Fiennes). Zero, a junior lobby boy, becomes Gustave&apos;s friend and protege. Gustave prides himself on providing first-class service to the hotel&apos;s guests, including satisfying the sexual needs of the many elderly women who stay there. When one of Gustave&apos;s lovers dies mysteriously, Gustave finds himself the recipient of a priceless painting and the chief suspect in her murder.</desc>
	</programme>
	<programme start="20230224221401 +0000" stop="20230225000601 +0000" start_timestamp="1677276841" stop_timestamp="1677283561" channel="Cinemax5StarMAX.us" >
		<title>The Card Counter</title>
		<desc>Movie (2021)
A gambler attempts to give guidance to a young man who is out for revenge against a mutual enemy.</desc>
	</programme>
	<programme start="20230225000601 +0000" stop="20230225020001 +0000" start_timestamp="1677283561" stop_timestamp="1677290401" channel="Cinemax5StarMAX.us" >
		<title>Memento</title>
		<desc>Movie (2000)
Leonard (Guy Pearce) is tracking down the man who raped and murdered his wife. The difficulty, however, of locating his wife&apos;s killer is compounded by the fact that he suffers from a rare, untreatable form of memory loss. Although he can recall details of life before his accident, Leonard cannot remember what happened fifteen minutes ago, where he&apos;s going, or why.</desc>
	</programme>
	<programme start="20230225020001 +0000" stop="20230225033901 +0000" start_timestamp="1677290401" stop_timestamp="1677296341" channel="Cinemax5StarMAX.us" >
		<title>What Happens in Vegas</title>
		<desc>Movie (2008)
During a wild vacation in Las Vegas, career woman Joy McNally (Cameron Diaz) and playboy Jack Fuller (Ashton Kutcher) come to the sober realization that they have married each other after a night of drunken abandon. Besides that, there is a huge jackpot at stake. An implacable judge freezes the prize money and refuses to grant an annulment, so Joy and Jack must try to make their impromptu marriage work.</desc>
	</programme>
	<programme start="20230225033901 +0000" stop="20230225050301 +0000" start_timestamp="1677296341" stop_timestamp="1677301381" channel="Cinemax5StarMAX.us" >
		<title>Dude, Where&apos;s My Car?</title>
		<desc>Movie (2000)
Last night, two party-hearty Dudes had an unbelievably sweet time. Too bad, they can&apos;t remember a thing, including where they parked their car. So, the Dudes embark on a mission: retrace their steps to find out what they did last night hoping it will lead them to the missing car. Little do the Dudes know, they&apos;re in for the ride of their lives.</desc>
	</programme>
	<programme start="20230225050301 +0000" stop="20230225063101 +0000" start_timestamp="1677301381" stop_timestamp="1677306661" channel="Cinemax5StarMAX.us" >
		<title>Throw Momma From the Train</title>
		<desc>Movie (1987)
Larry (Billy Crystal), an author with a cruel ex-wife, Margaret (Kate Mulgrew), teaches a writing workshop where Owen (Danny DeVito), one of his students, is fed up with his domineering mother (Anne Ramsey). When Owen watches a Hitchcock classic that seems to mirror his own life, he decides to put the movie&apos;s plot into action and offers to kill Margaret, if Larry promises to murder his mom. Before Larry gets a chance to react to the plan, it seems that Owen has already sealed Margaret&apos;s fate.</desc>
	</programme>
	<programme start="20230225063101 +0000" stop="20230225081701 +0000" start_timestamp="1677306661" stop_timestamp="1677313021" channel="Cinemax5StarMAX.us" >
		<title>Abduction</title>
		<desc>Movie (2011)
For many years, Nathan Harper (Taylor Lautner) has had the uneasy feeling that life with his family isn&apos;t quite what it seems. His fears come true when he finds a picture of himself as a youngster on a missing-persons website, proof that the people he&apos;s called mom and dad his whole life are not his real parents. As he draws close to uncovering his true identity, Nathan becomes the target of assassins, forcing him to flee with his neighbor, Karen (Lily Collins), the only person he can now trust.</desc>
	</programme>
	<programme start="20230225081701 +0000" stop="20230225095801 +0000" start_timestamp="1677313021" stop_timestamp="1677319081" channel="Cinemax5StarMAX.us" >
		<title>Righteous Kill</title>
		<desc>Movie (2008)
Detectives Thomas Cowan (Robert De Niro) and David Fisk (Al Pacino), 30-year veterans of the NYPD, investigate the murder of a pimp. The crime resembles a case they solved many years earlier. As the body count rises, they realize they&apos;re dealing with a vigilante taking over when the police fail. The similarities between past and present crimes leads the detectives to wonder if they put the wrong man behind bars.</desc>
	</programme>
	<programme start="20230225095801 +0000" stop="20230225114101 +0000" start_timestamp="1677319081" stop_timestamp="1677325261" channel="Cinemax5StarMAX.us" >
		<title>The Freshman</title>
		<desc>Movie (1990)
Clark Kellogg (Matthew Broderick) is robbed moments after arriving in New York, so when he sees his mugger several days later, he confronts him. The man promises to return his property and get him a job with his uncle, Carmine Sabatini (Marlon Brando), who turns out to be a Mafia boss. As Clark continues his shady work for Carmine, he discovers an elaborate underworld that has caught the attention of the authorities. As things come to a head, not everything is what it seems.</desc>
	</programme>
	<programme start="20230225114101 +0000" stop="20230225133101 +0000" start_timestamp="1677325261" stop_timestamp="1677331861" channel="Cinemax5StarMAX.us" >
		<title>Cats</title>
		<desc>Movie (2019)
A tribe of cats must decide yearly which one will ascend to the Heaviside Layer and come back to a new life.</desc>
	</programme>
</tv>